<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tick Track</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_label">Tick Track\n</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">Tick Track Description na wala pang nakalagay lmao</string>
    <string name="importance_of_accessibility">\tTick Track Service will be responsible for tracking and managing the restriction of applications. It detects whether the user opened a blocked application in the app itself. Without turning this service on, blocking apps would not be possible at all. This feature is the main highlight of the application. Therefore, everyone is encouraged to turn Tick Track Service on.</string>
    <string name="first_step">\tOnce you click the "Block Apps" button, it will take you to the accessibility settings. In there you need to find "Tick Track" to and enable it. </string>
    <string name="second_step">\tUnder downloaded apps, you should be able to see Tick Track. Tap the name of the app to turn it on.</string>
<string name="third_step">\tClick Tick Track, and turn on the switch.</string>
    <string name="fourth_step">\tA dialog would pop-up that would show what the service can do in the device. Tap allow to enable the service</string>
    <string name="fifth_step">\tAfter allowing the service to be enabled, the switch should turn on. You can now block applications through Tick Track application!</string>
    <string name="sixth_step">\tIn higher versions of Android, Google has been tightening up the security for accessibility. This message is always present in applications that are not put up in Google Play Store.</string>
    <string name="seventh_step">\tGo to settings and find Applications / Application Management.</string>
    <string name="eight_step">\tFind Applications List.</string>
    <string name="ninth_step">\tFind Tick Track application in the Applications List.</string>
    <string name="tenth_step">\tOnce you tap Tick Track, look for the 3-vertical dots at the upper-corner of the application info. Tap it.</string>
    <string name="eleventh_step">\tTap Unlock Restricted Setting / Allow Restricted Settings.</string>
    <string name="twelveth_step">\tIt should show a toast message at the bottom of the device. The application was now allowed to access restricted settings.</string>
    <string name="thirteenth_step">\tGo back to the app and tap \"Block Apps\" button again or go to Accessibility in Settings. Find Tick Track again and you should be able to turn it on now.</string>
    <string name="fourteenth_step">\tTurn on the switch of Tick Track and allow it to be enabled. You should be able to block and restrict applications now through the app itself.</string>


</resources>